He's going to need a vacation after this vacation.
Hotel Transylvania 3: Summer Vacation is a animation, comedy,
family film directed by Genndy Tartakovsky.
Dracula, Mavis, Johnny and the rest of the Drac Pack take a vacation on a luxury Monster Cruise Ship, where Dracula falls in love
with the ship’s captain, Ericka, who’s secretly a descendant of Abraham Van Helsing, the notorious monster slayer.
Count Dracula (voice), played by Adam Sandler.
Johnny Loughran (voice), played by Andy Samberg.
Mavis Dracula (voice), played by Selena Gomez.
Ericka Van Helsing (voice), played by Kathryn Hahn.
Professor Abraham Van Helsing (voice), played by Jim Gaffigan.
Frankenstein (voice), played by Kevin James.
Hotel Transylvania 3: Summer Vacation (released internationally as Hotel Transylvania 3: A Monster Vacation) is a 2018 American
animated monster comedy film directed by Genndy Tartakovsky and written by Tartakovsky and Michael McCullers.
Produced by Sony Pictures Animation, it is the third
film in the Hotel Transylvania franchise.
Adam Sandler, Andy Samberg, Selena Gomez, Kevin James, David Spade, Steve Buscemi, Keegan-Michael Key, Molly Shannon, Fran Drescher,
and Mel Brooks reprise their roles from previous installments, with Kathryn Hahn and Jim Gaffigan joining the cast.
In the film, Dracula finds love with a ship captain named Ericka while on a vacation on a luxury cruise liner with his family and
friends, but it is revealed that she is actually the great-granddaughter of his arch-nemesis, Abraham Van Helsing.
The film was announced in November 2015.
Tartakovsky confirmed his return in June 2016 after receiving inspiration from a
"miserable" family vacation and the Chevy Chase National Lampoon's Vacation movies.
The title was revealed in November 2017.
Hotel Transylvania 3: Summer Vacation premiered at the Annecy International Animation Film Festival
on June 13, 2018, and was theatrically released in the United States on July 13.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $528 million against a budget
of $65–80 million, making it the highest-grossing film in the series.
A further sequel, Hotel Transylvania: Transformania, was released in 2022, while a spin-off
series, Motel Transylvania, is scheduled to premiere on Netflix in 2027.
The film explores themes of monster, vampire, vacation, romance, cruise ship.
The tone is lighthearted.